a while ago I talked about why I thought
刚才我说到为什么我想
Toy Story 2 was an amazing Sequel and
不久前我谈到 为什么我认为玩具故事2 是一个惊人的塞克尔和
玩具故事2是一个惊人的塞克尔
Toy Story 2 was an amazing Sequel and
just a great movie overall but I haven't
玩具故事2是一个惊人的Sequel 和只是一个伟大的电影 整个电影,但我还没有
只是一部很棒的电影 总的来说,但我还没有
just a great movie overall but I haven't
yet talked about the other three Toy
只是一部很棒的电影 整个电影 但我还没有谈论过另外三个玩具
却谈论了另外三个玩具
yet talked about the other three Toy
Story movies and because I love this
却又谈了另外三部玩具故事电影 因为我喜欢这个
故事电影,因为我爱这个
Story movies and because I love this
franchise so much I full well intend to
故事电影,因为我爱这个特权 我完全想
专有权如此多,我完全 打算
franchise so much I full well intend to
discuss all of them but instead of going
如此多的特许经营权... ...我完全完全打算 讨论所有他们 而不是去...
讨论他们所有的问题,而不是去讨论他们所有的问题。
discuss all of them but instead of going
to one of the other two sequels I'd like
而不是去其他两个续集
给另外两个续集之一 我希望
to one of the other two sequels I'd like
to take a step back and talk about the
另外两个续集之一 我想退后一步 谈谈
后退一步,谈论
to take a step back and talk about the
first Toy Story movie instead and why I
后退一步 谈起第一部玩具故事电影
首部玩具故事电影 和为什么我
first Toy Story movie instead and why I
think that it is the perfect and
第一部玩具故事电影 和为什么我认为 它是完美的,
认为它是完美的,
think that it is the perfect and
ultimate tale of friendship such a basic
认为这是完美和终极的友谊故事 如此基本的
友谊的终极故事 如此基本的
ultimate tale of friendship such a basic
theme that is common in so many
友谊的终极故事,这样一个基本主题,在这么多人中是共同的
在许多主题中是相同的主题
theme that is common in so many
different stories and yet no story has
主题在如此多不同的故事中很常见,
不同的故事,但没有任何故事
different stories and yet no story has
ever done a tale of friendship as good
不同的故事,但没有任何故事 曾经做过一个友谊的故事 这么好
曾经做过一个友谊的故事
ever done a tale of friendship as good
as Toy Story you know at least that I've
做过一个和玩具故事一样美好的友谊故事 至少你知道,我
作为玩具故事 你至少知道我
as Toy Story you know at least that I've
seen anyways and so I thought why not
作为玩具故事,你至少知道 我见过,反正, 所以我想为什么不
无论如何,我总是看到,所以我想为什么不
seen anyways and so I thought why not
make a video trying to explain why it's
所以我想为什么不拍个视频 来解释为什么
制作一个视频 试图解释为什么它
make a video trying to explain why it's
totally not because my Pixar videos
一个视频试图解释为什么它完全不是因为我的Pixar视频。
完全不是因为我的 Pixar 视频
totally not because my Pixar videos
always perform better than the other
完全不是,因为我的Pixar视频 总是表现优于其他
表现总是优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优于优优于优于优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优优
always perform better than the other
videos I upload to this Channel or
总是比上传到此频道的其他视频效果更好, 或者
我上传到此频道或
videos I upload to this Channel or
anything
我上传到此频道或其它的视频
任何
anything
anyway Woody is probably one of my
伍迪可能是我的一个
反正伍迪可能是我的一个
anyway Woody is probably one of my
favorite fictional characters of all
反正伍迪可能是我最喜欢的虚构人物之一
全部最喜爱的虚构字符
favorite fictional characters of all
time and that is because of the intense
最喜爱的虚构角色 在所有的时间, 那是因为紧张
那是由於时间的紧张,
time and that is because of the intense
character development he goes through in
是因为他经历的 激烈的性格发展
他经历的个性发展
character development he goes through in
all three of the original movies the
他在所有三个原始电影中经历的 个性发展
所有三个原始电影 最初的电影
all three of the original movies the
fourth one is a little bit different
第四部片子有点不同
4号4号1有点不同
fourth one is a little bit different
though and we'll get to that one
4号1号4号4号1号有点不同,不过有点不同 我们会找到那个的
尽管我们会得到那个
though and we'll get to that one
eventually but as for how he is in this
虽然我们最终会找到那个 但是关于他现在的处境
至於他怎样在火狱中呢?
eventually but as for how he is in this
movie one thing I really appreciate
最后,关于他怎么在这部电影里 我非常欣赏他
电影,一件事 我真的很感激
movie one thing I really appreciate
about his character is how he isn't
电影电影,我真的很欣赏他 性格的一面,就是他不是
因为他的性格,所以他不是
about his character is how he isn't
really that lovable hero that everyone
因为他的性格,他不是那么可爱的英雄
真正可爱的英雄 每个人
really that lovable hero that everyone
knows him as yet he's actually quite
真正可爱的英雄 每个人都知道他 至今他实际上相当
其实他还很了解他
knows him as yet he's actually quite
selfish and stubborn at the start of
他其实很自私,很固执
开始的时候自私固执
selfish and stubborn at the start of
this movie and it primarily stems from
在这部电影的开头, 自私和固执的自私 和固执地在这部电影的开头, 它主要起源于
这部电影主要起源于
this movie and it primarily stems from
the fact that he has influence and power
这部电影主要源于他有影响力和权力
他有影响,有权力,
the fact that he has influence and power
and as far as we know Woody has never
事实上,他有影响力和权力 就我们所知,伍迪从来没有
据我们所知伍迪从未
and as far as we know Woody has never
not had the influence and power that he
据我们所知 伍迪从未拥有过 他那种影响力和权力
他没有影响,没有权力,
not had the influence and power that he
currently has because ever since he has
他现在没有他现在拥有的影响力和权力,因为他从那时起就拥有了
因为他从那时起
currently has because ever since he has
been here he has been Andy's favorite
因为自从他来后 他一直是安迪的最爱
来过这里,他一直是安迪的最爱
been here he has been Andy's favorite
toy and by being Andy's favorite toy it
他是安迪最喜欢的玩具 也是安迪最喜欢的玩具
玩具是安迪最喜欢的玩具
toy and by being Andy's favorite toy it
puts him in a position of influence and
玩具和安迪最喜欢的玩具 使他处于有影响力的地位
使他处于有影响力的地位,
puts him in a position of influence and
power over all the other toys and so
将他置于对所有其他玩具有影响力和权力的地位,
在所有其它玩具上的力量等等
power over all the other toys and so
whether he realizes it or not he has
超越所有其他玩具的力量 所以他是否意识到他有
难道他知道吗?如果他有,
whether he realizes it or not he has
come to believe that he is actually
他是否意识到,他是否已经相信,他实际上是
相信他其实
come to believe that he is actually
better than the other toys but what
相信他其实比其他玩具好 但是什么
比其他玩具更好,但什么
better than the other toys but what
makes his Dynamic with the other toys so
比其他玩具更好 但是什么使得 他与其他玩具的动态
他用其他玩具来创造他的活力,所以
makes his Dynamic with the other toys so
interesting and not some sort of
他与其他玩具的动态 如此有趣,而不是某种
而不是某种有趣的,而不是某种
interesting and not some sort of
villainous role like he was actually
而不是像他那样的恶毒角色
像他那样的恶毒角色
villainous role like he was actually
originally intended to be before they
像他那样的恶毒角色 本来是想在他们面前扮演的
原原打算摆在他们面前
originally intended to be before they
changed the script is that the other
原本打算在他们改变剧本之前
修改的脚本是另一个
changed the script is that the other
toys for the most part like and respect
剧本更改的剧本是其他玩具 大部分是喜欢和尊重的
大部分玩具 喜欢和尊重的玩具
toys for the most part like and respect
him because he treats them all well
大部分玩具都喜欢他 尊重他 因为他对待他们都很好
因为他善待他们,
him because he treats them all well
however as we will soon discover the
因为他善待他们,无论我们怎样发现,他不久就发现,
然而,当我们不久发现
however as we will soon discover the
primary reason why he treats everyone
然而,我们很快会发现 他对待每个人的主要原因
他对待每个人的首要原因
primary reason why he treats everyone
well is because he has never seen seen
因为他从未见过
anyone as a threat to his power they've
因为他从未见过任何人 威胁他的权力
任何威胁他的力量的人
anyone as a threat to his power they've
always been quote unquote beneath him
任何威胁他力量的人... ...他们总是在他下面被引用
一直以来都是他下面的引文
always been quote unquote beneath him
and so he has always felt this need to
所以他一直觉得有必要
因此,他始终认为有必要
and so he has always felt this need to
take care of everyone else to be the
所以他一直认为 照顾其他人
照顾其他人
take care of everyone else to be the
leader and while he is very good at
照顾其他人 成为领袖 当他非常擅长
当他精明领导,而且善于领导的时候,
leader and while he is very good at
doing that job the fact that he has
当他非常擅长做那份工作时
做这份工作的事实
doing that job the fact that he has
never been challenged has caused his ego
他从未受到挑战的事实 引起了他的自我
从未受到挑战 已经引起他的自我
never been challenged has caused his ego
to become inflated as soon as Buzz shows
从未被挑战过 已经引起他的自我膨胀 一旦巴斯显示
等巴兹一露面 就会膨胀
to become inflated as soon as Buzz shows
up he doesn't do anything wrong he just
等巴兹一露面 就不会做错任何事
他没有做错什么 只是他没有做错什么
up he doesn't do anything wrong he just
introduces himself to the other toys but
他没有做错什么 他只是介绍自己 其他玩具,但
向他人介绍其他玩具,但
introduces himself to the other toys but
Woody having seen that he took his place
介绍自己认识其他玩具 但伍迪看到自己取代了自己
伍迪看到他取代了自己的位置
Woody having seen that he took his place
immediately becomes paranoid of the idea
伍迪看到了他取代了自己的位置 立刻就变得偏执了这个想法
立即成为这个想法的偏执偏执
immediately becomes paranoid of the idea
of being replaced something he
立即成为偏执的偏执 的想法 被替换的东西,他
被取代的东西,他
of being replaced something he
ironically told everyone else wouldn't
被取代的东西 他讽刺地告诉 其他人不会
讽刺地告诉大家 其他人不会
ironically told everyone else wouldn't
happen but that's because he's never
讽刺讽刺地告诉其他人不会发生 但那是因为他从来没有
因为他从来没有
happen but that's because he's never
thought anyone could ever replace him he
因为他从未想过 任何人能取代他
以为任何人都可以取代他
thought anyone could ever replace him he
only saw the other toys as being
以为有人能代替他 他只看到其他玩具
只看到其他玩具
only saw the other toys as being
replaceable and would be the one to step
只认为其他玩具是可替代的, 并会是一个步骤
可替代的,并且将是一个步骤
replaceable and would be the one to step
up to defend them but who's going to
可以替代 并且会是一个 站出来保护他们的人 但谁要
谁能保护他们呢? 谁能保护他们呢?
up to defend them but who's going to
defend him if he's already the best and
但是谁来保护他 如果他已经是最好的了
如果他已经是最好的了
defend him if he's already the best and
I just love the subtle Touch of how
如果他已经是最好的了,我爱他 保护他,如果他已经是最好的,我只是喜欢 微妙的触碰如何
我只是喜欢 微妙的触摸如何
I just love the subtle Touch of how
Woody is constantly trying to put Buzz
我喜欢胡迪一直试图把巴兹
伍迪一直想把巴兹
Woody is constantly trying to put Buzz
down in his first introduction without
伍迪一直试图 将巴斯在第一次介绍时
在他的第一次介绍中
down in his first introduction without
ever explicitly stating so as his first
在第一次介绍时,他从未明确地说这是他的第一次。
曾明确地说,这是他的第一次
ever explicitly stating so as his first
thought is to make Buzz out to be lesser
他第一次想让巴兹变小
意思是让巴斯变小
thought is to make Buzz out to be lesser
than him so that no one thinks that he
以为是让巴斯比他小,所以没有人认为他
以免任何人比他更确信他,
than him so that no one thinks that he
could be better or take his place and
以免任何人认为他更好,或代替他,
可能更好,或取代他的位置,
could be better or take his place and
when this fails Woody feels genuine fear
或取代他的位置 当他失败时 伍迪感到真正的恐惧
当胡迪感到真正的恐惧
when this fails Woody feels genuine fear
for the first time all who gain power
当这个失败的胡迪 第一次感到真正的恐惧 所有获得权力的人
第一次,所有掌权者,
for the first time all who gain power
are afraid to lose it and this is when
第一次 所有掌权者 害怕失去权力
害怕失去它 而此时
are afraid to lose it and this is when
the song strange things plays which is
害怕失去它 而这就是当歌曲 奇怪的事物播放
歌唱着奇奇怪怪的东西演奏着
the song strange things plays which is
not just a really solid song on its own
歌唱着奇奇事物的演奏 不只是一首真正的实实在在的歌
不只是一首真正的坚固的歌
not just a really solid song on its own
but has a clever twist to it if you pay
不仅仅是一首真正的坚固的歌 如果你付钱的话
但要是付了钱,就有一个巧妙的曲折
but has a clever twist to it if you pay
attention because you see the song
但要是看一眼看这首歌 就会有很巧妙的曲折
因为你看到这首歌
attention because you see the song
itself uses the unreliable narrator
因为你看到这首歌本身 使用不可靠的旁听者
利用不可靠的旁白者
itself uses the unreliable narrator
Trope in which something is being said
使用不可靠的旁白人Trope,其中有人在说些什么
突然间,有人在说些什么
Trope in which something is being said
as fact when in reality it is actually
在现实中,在现实中,有些事情被说成是事实
事实上,当现实中,它实际上是
as fact when in reality it is actually
only the perspective and opinion of a
事实上,在现实中,事实上它实际上仅仅是一个个人的观点和观点。
观点和意见的见解、见解、见解、见解、见解、见解、见解、
only the perspective and opinion of a
single character not only is this song
这首歌不单是单一个角色的视角和观点 这首歌不单是这首歌
这首歌不单是单单字符
single character not only is this song
the proof that we know that Woody has
不仅这首歌能证明我们知道伍迪
证明我们知道胡迪有
the proof that we know that Woody has
never had to encounter a situation where
证明我们知道胡迪从未遇到过
从未遇到过这样的情况
never had to encounter a situation where
someone was seen on the same level as
从未遇到过这样的情况,即人们看到某人的级别与《公约》和《公约》的级别相同。
同一级别上的人被看见
someone was seen on the same level as
him before but it also reveals to us how
也向我们揭示了
在他之前,他确已降示我们,它能昭示我们怎样的、
him before but it also reveals to us how
Woody sees his own power and influence
在他之前,他虽能见,却能见我们,它能见胡迪怎样看待他的权力和影响力。
伍迪看到了自己的力量和影响力
Woody sees his own power and influence
in a way that reveals that it is not
伍迪认为自己的权力和影响力 表明它不是
以显示它不是
in a way that reveals that it is not
nearly as strong as he thinks it is
显示它并不像他所想的那么强大
和他所想的一样强大
nearly as strong as he thinks it is
because the song claims that he had all
和他所想的一样强大 因为那首歌声称他拥有所有
因为那首歌声称他拥有
because the song claims that he had all
these great things before but not
因为歌声声称 他拥有所有这些伟大的事物 之前,但没有
这些伟大的事,以前没有,但以前没有;
these great things before but not
anymore but just because Buzz showed up
这些伟大的事物以前 但不再是现在了 只是因为巴斯出现了
但仅仅因为巴斯出现了
anymore but just because Buzz showed up
doesn't mean he no longer has power or
但仅仅因为巴斯出现了 并不意味着他不再有权力或权力
并不意味着他不再有权力或权力
doesn't mean he no longer has power or
respect unless of course he never
并不意味着他不再有权力或尊重 除非他从来没有
当然,除非他从未
respect unless of course he never
actually had that in the first place and
当然,除非他从未真正拥有过
从一开始,
actually had that in the first place and
people only presumed that he had power
一开始人们只假设他有权力
人只以为他有权力
people only presumed that he had power
and respect because he was the only only
人们只是假设他有权力和尊敬 因为他是唯一
因为他是唯一
and respect because he was the only only
one on that same level being Andy's
因为他是唯一一个 和Andy一样的
和Andy的同一水平
one on that same level being Andy's
favorite toy but now that there's
Andy最喜欢的玩具 但现在有
最喜欢的玩具 但现在有
favorite toy but now that there's
someone else Woody perceives that all
最最喜欢的玩具 但现在有别人 伍迪觉得
伍迪认为
someone else Woody perceives that all
his power and respect is gone because
伍迪认为他所有的权力和尊敬都消失了 因为
他的力量和尊敬 已经消失,因为
his power and respect is gone because
people only pay attention to Buzz
因为人们只关注巴斯
人们只关注巴斯
people only pay attention to Buzz
Lightyear now respect is not something
人们只关注巴斯光年 现在尊重不是一件好事
光年不是什么光年 尊重不是什么好事
Lightyear now respect is not something
you lose by someone else supposedly
光年现在 尊重不是别人所失去的
被别人迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷迷
you lose by someone else supposedly
better than you showing up and taking it
被别人甩掉 比你现身和接受的好
比你现身和采取它更好
better than you showing up and taking it
all away if someone truly respects you
如果有人真正尊敬你 比你现身 拿走一切好
如果有人真正尊敬你
all away if someone truly respects you
then they'll respect you so long as you
如果有人真正尊重你,他们就会尊重你 只要你
他们就会尊重你,只要你
then they'll respect you so long as you
don't contradict the aspects of yourself
他们就会尊重你 只要你不自相矛盾
不要自相矛盾
don't contradict the aspects of yourself
that they respect you can perfectly see
不要自相矛盾的方面 他们尊重你,你可以完全看得见
他们尊重你,你完全可以看见
that they respect you can perfectly see
this Dynamic through many of the other
他们尊重你 能够完全看透这个动态 通过其他的很多
透过其他许多
this Dynamic through many of the other
toys on one end you have someone like Bo
通过其他很多玩具的这种动态 通过在一端的很多玩具 你有一个像博这样的人
在一端的玩具 你有一个像波这样的人
toys on one end you have someone like Bo
Peep who clearly actually does respect
在一端的玩具 你有一个像Bo Peep这样的人 很明显他确实尊重
佩佩谁显然 实际确实尊重
Peep who clearly actually does respect
Woody because even after he knocks Buzz
很明显谁真的尊重伍迪 因为他敲了巴兹之后
伍迪因为即使他敲了巴兹
Woody because even after he knocks Buzz
out the window and becomes lost she
伍迪因为即使他把巴兹打出窗外 迷了路
她从窗外迷路了,
out the window and becomes lost she
hasn't turned against him and gives him
她没有背叛他,没有给予他
没有背叛他,没有给予他
hasn't turned against him and gives him
the benefit of the doubt that it really
并没有背叛他 反而让他怀疑
怀疑它是否真的
the benefit of the doubt that it really
was a mistake because she trusts what he
因为她相信他所相信的
是个错误 因为她相信他
was a mistake because she trusts what he
says then you have someone like Slinky
那是个错误 因为她相信他说的话 然后你就会有斯林基这样的人
说你有个像斯林奇这样的人
says then you have someone like Slinky
who did seem to have some level of
说你有个像斯林基这样的人 似乎有一定的
似乎有某种程度的
who did seem to have some level of
respect for Woody before but this level
他们似乎对伍迪有某种程度的尊重 但是这个程度
之前对胡迪的尊敬, 但在此水平下
respect for Woody before but this level
of respect was lost when he saw that
以前尊重胡迪,但当他看到
当他看到
of respect was lost when he saw that
Woody seem to contradict himself with
当他看到伍迪似乎与
伍迪似乎自相矛盾
Woody seem to contradict himself with
everything that he did and set against
伍迪似乎自相矛盾 他所做的一切 并开始反对
他所行的善功,而且加以反驳,
everything that he did and set against
Buzz Lightyear and of course on the
他所做的一切 并设置 与巴斯光年 和当然在
巴斯光年 当然还有
Buzz Lightyear and of course on the
complete other end of the spectrum from
巴斯光年 当然还有另一端的光谱
频谱从
complete other end of the spectrum from
Bo Peep is someone like Mr Potato Head
博比普的光谱的另一端 是马铃薯头先生这样的人
Bo Peep是像土豆头一样的人
Bo Peep is someone like Mr Potato Head
who never respected Woody and always saw
Bo Peep是像马铃薯头这样的人 他从不尊重伍迪 总是看到
永远不尊重胡迪 并且总是看到
who never respected Woody and always saw
his level of power and influence as
永远不尊重胡迪 始终认为他的权力和影响力
他的权力和影响力的程度,以及
his level of power and influence as
something that was not really a as
他的权力和影响力 并不像一个
某种非真正属于
something that was not really a as
strong as Woody had made it out to be
并不像伍迪想的那样强大
就像伍迪所想的那样
strong as Woody had made it out to be
another great example of how Woody's
就像伍迪所展示的 伍迪如何成为另一个伟大的榜样一样
伍迪的又一大例子
another great example of how Woody's
respect and power was never as strong as
伍迪的尊敬和权力 从来没有这么强大过
尊重和权力从没有像现在这样强大
respect and power was never as strong as
he believed it was comes right after the
尊重和权力从没有像他相信的那么强大
他相信它就在
he believed it was comes right after the
song strange things where the shark
他相信歌声之后就传来 鲨鱼在那里的奇奇怪怪的东西
歌唱奇怪的事情 在那里鲨鱼
song strange things where the shark
character takes Woody's hat and mocks
歌唱奇怪的事情 鲨鱼的角色 拿走胡迪的帽子和假帽子
将伍迪的帽子和假帽子
character takes Woody's hat and mocks
him with it if Woody really was as
如果伍迪真的像
如果伍迪真的和他在一起
him with it if Woody really was as
perfect as he thought he was then other
如果伍迪真的和他想象的一样完美
完美如他以为自己是另一个人
perfect as he thought he was then other
toys like this shark wouldn't so easily
就像他以为自己是其他玩具一样完美 就像这只鲨鱼不会那么容易
像这只鲨鱼这样的玩具不会那么容易
toys like this shark wouldn't so easily
be making fun of him and speaking of
像这鲨鱼这样的玩具 不会那么容易取笑他 说到
取笑他,说着
be making fun of him and speaking of
Buzz one thing I really like about him
取笑他 说到巴兹 我非常喜欢他
巴斯有一件事我很喜欢他
Buzz one thing I really like about him
is how just like Woody he has some sort
巴斯,我最喜欢他一件事 就是像伍迪一样
就像伍迪一样,他有某种
is how just like Woody he has some sort
of prominent character flaw the fact
就像伍迪一样 他有突出的性格
显着特征的突出特征 使事实的缺陷
of prominent character flaw the fact
that he can't see that he isn't just a
突出人物的突出性格 瑕疵的事实, 他看不到 他不只是一个
他看不到他不只是个
that he can't see that he isn't just a
toy and actually thinks he's a Space
他看不到自己不只是个玩具 而且实际上认为自己是个太空人
玩具,实际上认为他是一个太空人
toy and actually thinks he's a Space
Ranger making it so that neither of the
玩具,实际上认为他是太空游骑兵,所以
游骑兵制造它,这样两个都没有
Ranger making it so that neither of the
main characters are perfectly in the
游骑兵制造它,使 没有一个主要人物是完美的在
主字符在
main characters are perfectly in the
right or completely in the wrong and
主字符完全正确或完全错误,
或完全在迷误中,
right or completely in the wrong and
another thing that makes Buzz work so
或完全在错误 和另一件事 使巴斯的工作如此
另一件事让巴斯如此工作
another thing that makes Buzz work so
well as a character is that his delusion
另一件事让巴斯工作 如此好的一个性格 就是他的错觉
和性格是他的错觉
well as a character is that his delusion
that he is a Space Ranger isn't his only
以及一个性格 就是他的幻觉 认为自己是太空游骑兵不是他唯一的
他是一个太空游骑兵 不是他唯一的
that he is a Space Ranger isn't his only
flaw because he's also very stubborn as
他是个太空游骑兵 并不是他唯一的缺陷 因为他也非常固执
因为他也非常固执
flaw because he's also very stubborn as
well because he is so determined to
因为他也非常固执 因为他决心要
因为他下定决心
well because he is so determined to
prove that he's actually a Space Ranger
因为他如此决心 证明他实际上是一个太空游骑兵
证明他其实是个太空游骑兵
prove that he's actually a Space Ranger
he fails to see that Woody is simply
证明他其实是个太空游骑兵 他看不到伍迪只是
他看不到胡迪只是
he fails to see that Woody is simply
trying to tell him the truth of his
他看不到胡迪只是 试图告诉他他的真相
以便他把他的宗教,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,和真主,都说他的宗教,和他的主的宗教,和他的主的宗教,都说:他的主的宗教的宗教的宗教,说他的主的宗教的宗教,说他的主的宗教的宗教,说他的主的宗教的宗教,说他的主的宗教的宗教,说他的主的,
trying to tell him the truth of his
reality and he instead takes it as a
试图告诉他他真实的真相,而他却把它当作
而他却把它当作一个现实
reality and he instead takes it as a
personal attack on his character of
相反,他把它当作是个人攻击,攻击他的个性
侵犯其个人人格的人身攻击
personal attack on his character of
course what he wasn't exactly relaying
个人攻击他的性格 当然,他没有 确切的中继
说明他到底没有转接什么
course what he wasn't exactly relaying
this information in the right way but
说明他没有正确传达这些信息 但是
这种信息是用正确的方式提供的,
this information in the right way but
Buzz is in the Raw when it comes to
这个消息是真实的,当消息来临的时候,巴斯在罗河里。
说到巴斯,巴斯在罗罗里
Buzz is in the Raw when it comes to
hearing out other points of view that
巴斯在罗尔 听到其他观点时
提出了其他观点,
hearing out other points of view that
contradict his own and this causes him
听取其他与他本人的观点相矛盾的观点,并因此引起他
故他自相矛盾,故他自相矛盾,
contradict his own and this causes him
to reject the idea of what he ever
他自相矛盾,因此,他否认自己所崇拜的(偶像),
以否认他所崇拜的(偶像)盟誓,
to reject the idea of what he ever
becoming his friend quite early on and I
拒绝他早早成为朋友的想法
我早早成为他的朋友
becoming his friend quite early on and I
also love the small progression of how
早早成为他的朋友 我也喜欢这小小的进展
也爱着微小的进化
also love the small progression of how
Woody sees Buzz's belief that he's a
也爱着伍迪如何看待巴兹 相信他是一个
胡迪看到巴兹相信他是个
Woody sees Buzz's belief that he's a
Space Ranger first thinking it's all
胡迪看到了巴斯的信念 他是一个太空游骑兵
太空游骑兵先想
Space Ranger first thinking it's all
just an act and playing it up to make
太空游骑兵首先认为这只是个表演 玩它来制造
只是一个表演 玩它来制造
just an act and playing it up to make
himself look cool he's not a Space
只是演戏,玩起来让自己看起来很酷 他不是一个太空人
自己看起来很酷,他不是太空人
himself look cool he's not a Space
Ranger he doesn't fight evil or shoot
自己看起来很酷,他不是太空游骑兵,他不与邪恶战斗,也不开枪
游骑兵,他不与邪恶战斗,也不开枪
Ranger he doesn't fight evil or shoot
lasers or fly but then realizing that he
游骑兵他不与邪恶战斗 也不发射激光或飞翔 但后来意识到他
激光或飞行,但后来意识到他
lasers or fly but then realizing that he
genuinely actually believes it and using
激光或飞行,但随后意识到 他真的相信它,并使用它
真正相信并使用
genuinely actually believes it and using
this as a chance to mock him and once
真正相信它 利用它来嘲笑他 一次
这是一次嘲笑他的机会
this as a chance to mock him and once
again try to make him look lesser than
这是一次嘲笑他的机会 并再次试图让他看起来弱于
试图让他看起来小于
again try to make him look lesser than
himself hey guys look it's the real Buzz
试着让他看起来比自己小 嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿,这是真正的巴斯
嘿伙计们,看这是真正的巴斯
himself hey guys look it's the real Buzz
Lightyear and of course when they get
嘿伙计们,看这是真正的巴斯光年 当然,当他们得到
光年,当然,当他们得到
Lightyear and of course when they get
lost just completely losing it because
光年,当然,当他们迷失了 只是完全失去它,因为
完全失去,因为
lost just completely losing it because
he can't stand it anymore according to
完全失去 完全失去 因为他再也受不了了
他再也受不了了
he can't stand it anymore according to
my Nava computer shut up
根据我纳瓦电脑闭嘴的说法 他再也受不了了
我的纳瓦电脑闭嘴
my Nava computer shut up
shut up you idiot and speaking of
我的纳瓦电脑闭嘴,闭嘴,你这个白痴,说
闭上你这白痴的嘴 说到
shut up you idiot and speaking of
getting lost one thing I really like
闭上你这白痴的嘴 说要失去我最喜欢的一件事
失去我最喜欢的一件事
getting lost one thing I really like
about the part where woody knocks Buzz
失去一件事 我真的很喜欢 木棍敲巴兹的那部分
有关木木敲巴兹的部分
about the part where woody knocks Buzz
out the window is that it both was
木林敲敲木头的部分 巴斯走出窗口 巴斯是,它两者都是
窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗窗
out the window is that it both was
intentional and an accident at the same
窗外的窗外是,它既是故意的,也是一起意外
同一事故发生时的故意事故和意外事故
intentional and an accident at the same
time this is genius because it causes
同时也是故意和意外的意外 这是天才,因为它导致
这是天才 因为它导致
time this is genius because it causes
Woody to know that he is guilty but also
这是天才的时机 因为它让伍迪知道 他有罪,但也有罪
伍迪知道他有罪 但也知道他有罪
Woody to know that he is guilty but also
be able to trick himself into believing
伍迪知道自己有罪 但也能够欺骗自己去相信
能够欺骗自己去信道,
be able to trick himself into believing
that he wasn't guilty because it kind of
能够欺骗自己 相信他无罪 因为它有点
因为他没有罪过 因为它有点
that he wasn't guilty because it kind of
was an accident how am I gonna convince
我该怎么说服他
是个意外 我怎么能说服
was an accident how am I gonna convince
those guys it was an accident thus
我该怎么说服那些家伙 那是个意外
那些家伙,所以那是个意外
those guys it was an accident thus
creating a great inner conflict in him
那些家伙,那是个意外 从而在他体内制造了一场巨大的内部冲突
在他的内心制造了一场巨大的内部冲突
creating a great inner conflict in him
that continues to boil up until the
在他的内心制造了一场巨大的内部冲突 一直持续到
一直到现在
that continues to boil up until the
climax of the film another thing that
直到电影的高潮 还有一件事
电影的高潮 另一件事
climax of the film another thing that
this scene reveals to us is something
这部电影的高潮 另一件事 这场景向我们揭示
这个场景向我们揭示了
this scene reveals to us is something
that many people seem to forget that all
这个场景向我们揭示了 许多人似乎忘记了
许多人似乎忘记了
that many people seem to forget that all
these other toys in Andy's room aren't
很多人似乎忘记了 Andy房间里的这些玩具
安迪房间里的这些玩具不是
these other toys in Andy's room aren't
actually Woody's friends at least not
安迪房间里的其他玩具 其实不是伍迪的朋友 至少不是
其实伍迪的朋友 至少不是
actually Woody's friends at least not
true friends of his because if they were
事实上伍迪的朋友 至少不是他真正的朋友 因为如果他们是
他真正的朋友,因为如果他们是
true friends of his because if they were
then they wouldn't have tried to throw
他真正的朋友,因为如果他们是朋友, 他们就不会试图扔
那样他们就不会想扔了
then they wouldn't have tried to throw
him out the window fearing for their
然后他们就不会试图把他扔出窗外 害怕他们
他为怕他们而从窗外出去,
him out the window fearing for their
lives it shows that Woody's assumed
说明伍迪的假设
power and influence over them isn't as
伍迪的权势和影响力
影响他们的力量和影响力
power and influence over them isn't as
strong as he actually thought because he
影响他们的力量和影响力 并没有他想象的那么强大 因为他
因为他真的想,
strong as he actually thought because he
never actually took the time to build a
因为他从来没有花过时间来建造
从来没有花过时间来建造
never actually took the time to build a
true relationship with any of them
从来没有花过时间 和其中任何一个 建立真正的关系
与他们中任何等人,
true relationship with any of them
except maybe Bo Peep another great thing
他们中除博比外,有许多人,的确与他们中的任何人,确是有关系,但有别的伟大的(偶像),
也许除了波比还有一件伟大的事
except maybe Bo Peep another great thing
about this Woody knocking Buzz outside
除了博比也许还有一件伟大的事情 关于这个伍迪敲外面的巴兹
关于这个胡迪敲钟 外面的巴斯
about this Woody knocking Buzz outside
the window scene is that even though
关于这个伍迪敲门巴兹 在窗外的 窗口场景是,即使
窗口的场景是,即使
the window scene is that even though
Woody basically got what he wanted being
虽然伍迪得到了他想要的
伍迪得到了他想要的
Woody basically got what he wanted being
taken by Andy to Pizza Planet instead of
伍迪基本上得到了他想要的东西 被安迪带到比萨星球 而不是
安迪带去比萨星球 而不是
taken by Andy to Pizza Planet instead of
Buzz he isn't actually satisfied or
安迪被带去比萨星球 而不是巴斯 他实际上并不满意
巴斯,他实际上不满意,或
Buzz he isn't actually satisfied or
happy because of the fact that all the
巴斯,他实际上并不满意或快乐 因为事实上,所有
快乐,因为事实上,所有
happy because of the fact that all the
other toys turned on him and so neither
因为所有其它玩具 都向他倾斜 所以都没有
其它玩具都对他发火了,所以他也没有发火
other toys turned on him and so neither
character actually gets what they wanted
其它玩具都对他发脾气 所以两个性格都没有真正得到他们想要的东西
性格实际上得到了他们想要的
character actually gets what they wanted
having both Woody and Buzz become lost
真正得到他们想要的东西 伍迪和巴兹都迷失了
胡迪和巴兹都迷失了方向
having both Woody and Buzz become lost
and separated from Andy and all the
伍迪和巴兹都迷失了 与安迪和所有
与安迪和众人分离,
and separated from Andy and all the
other toys is a perfect way of forcing
与安迪和所有其他玩具分离 是一种完美的强迫方式
其他玩具是强迫的完美方法
other toys is a perfect way of forcing
Woody into a situation where he can't
其他玩具是逼胡迪进入他无法进入的状态的完美方法
伍迪陷入一个他不能
Woody into a situation where he can't
get what he wants without Buzz Lightyear
伍迪陷入了这样的境地 没有巴斯光年 他得不到他想要的东西
没有巴斯光年 得到他想要的
get what he wants without Buzz Lightyear
or else no one will believe him and all
没有巴斯光年,没人会相信他
不然,任何人不能信仰他,任何人不能信仰他,
or else no one will believe him and all
throughout this scene at the gas station
否则没人会相信他 和在加油站的整场戏
在加油站的这整个场景中
throughout this scene at the gas station
the only thing Woody ever thinks about
在加油站的这个场景 胡迪唯一想到的
胡迪唯一想过的事
the only thing Woody ever thinks about
is how he's going to fix his problem how
伍迪唯一想到的 就是如何解决他的问题
他会如何解决他的问题 如何
is how he's going to fix his problem how
he's going to get back what's going to
他将如何解决自己的问题 如何回到过去
他会回到过去 回到过去
he's going to get back what's going to
happen to him completely all
他会得到回来 会发生什么 他将完全发生在他身上
完全发生在他身上
happen to him completely all
self-absorbed thoughts he doesn't care a
在他身上发生 所有的自食其果的想法 他不在乎
自我吸收的想法 他不在乎一个
self-absorbed thoughts he doesn't care a
smidge about Buzz Lightyear he's just a
他对巴斯光年毫不关心 他只是个
有关巴斯光年的惊吓,他只是一个
smidge about Buzz Lightyear he's just a
tool for him to use to get back to where
关于巴斯光年的惊吓 巴斯光年只是他用来 回到哪里的工具
用于返回位置的工具
tool for him to use to get back to where
he was and regain his reputation and
并恢复他的声誉。
并恢复他的名誉,
he was and regain his reputation and
power meanwhile Buzz without technically
恢复他的声誉和权力 同时巴兹没有技术上的
巴斯没有技术上的
power meanwhile Buzz without technically
still delusional over the idea of being
巴斯在技术上 仍没有妄想 认为自己是
仍然幻想着
still delusional over the idea of being
a Space Ranger actually does care he
仍然幻想着 成为太空游骑兵的想法 实际上确实在意他
a 太空巡警确实关心他
a Space Ranger actually does care he
cares about saving the entire universe
a 太空游骑兵确实在乎 他关心拯救整个宇宙
关心拯救整个宇宙
cares about saving the entire universe
even if there isn't actually anyone to
拯救整个宇宙的关心 即使实际上没有人
即使实际上没有人
even if there isn't actually anyone to
save and there's nothing he could really
即使实际上没有人可以救他 也没什么他能真正救他
并没有什么 他能够真正
save and there's nothing he could really
do because it's all fictional the fact
并且他什么也做不了 因为这都是虚构的事实
因为这都是虚构的事实
do because it's all fictional the fact
of the matter is the mindset of the two
因为它都是虚构的 事实的事实 问题的事实是 两种思想的心态
问题是双方的心态,
of the matter is the mindset of the two
characters the problem is neither
问题是两个角色的心态 问题不是两个
字符 问题不是两个字符
characters the problem is neither
mindset is actually going to help them
问题在于个性, 问题不是心态, 是否真的会帮助他们
他们的心态其实会帮助他们
mindset is actually going to help them
get what they want or overcome their
实际上,他们的心态实际上会帮助他们得到他们想要的,或克服他们想要的,或克服他们想要的。
获得他们想要或克服的财富,
get what they want or overcome their
flaws and of course Woody finds this out
得到他们想要得到的东西或克服他们的缺陷,当然胡迪会发现这一点。
伍迪当然会发现
flaws and of course Woody finds this out
the hard way at Pizza Planet where both
当然,伍迪发现这 在比萨星球的艰难方式
《比萨星球》的艰难之路
the hard way at Pizza Planet where both
of them focusing exclusively on their
在《比萨星球》上 两人都专注于
专门专注于《公约》和《经济、社会、文化权利
of them focusing exclusively on their
own goals gets them into trouble instead
他们只专注于自己的目标,反而使他们陷入麻烦之中。
目标本身的目标反而使他们陷入麻烦之中。
own goals gets them into trouble instead
of fixing the problem and now we've
自己的目标 让他们陷入麻烦 而不是解决问题 现在我们已经
解决问题,现在我们
of fixing the problem and now we've
reached the part where Buzz and Woody
解决问题 现在我们到达了巴斯和伍迪
到达了巴兹和胡迪所在的部分
reached the part where Buzz and Woody
end up in Sid's house now this
到了巴兹和胡迪 来到西德家的那部分 现在这个
现在在席德的家,现在这个
end up in Sid's house now this
originally used to be my least favorite
死在Sid家 现在这个原来是我最不喜欢的
本来是我最不喜欢的
originally used to be my least favorite
part of the movie since most of the
原本是我最不喜欢的电影部分 因为大部分
电影的一部分 因为大部分
part of the movie since most of the
funniest parts are in the first half and
电影的一部分 因为大多数有趣的部分 在上半和
最有趣的部分在前半和
funniest parts are in the first half and
this was the slowest part of the movie
最有趣的部分在上半部 这是电影中最慢的部分
这是电影中最慢的部分
this was the slowest part of the movie
overall but these days I've kind of
这是整个电影中 最慢的部分 但最近我有点
总的来说,但最近我有点...
overall but these days I've kind of
reversed my opinion while the first half
总的来说,但最近我改变了我的看法 上半年我改变了我的看法
我的意见被推翻,而上半年
reversed my opinion while the first half
is still just as good as it always was
我的意见被推翻,而前半部分仍然和往常一样好
仍然和以前一样好
is still just as good as it always was
the second half might actually be the
仍然和后半年一样好
后半段可能其实是
the second half might actually be the
superior half of the movie in my opinion
下半部实际上可能是 电影的上半部 在我看来
在我看来 这部电影的上上半部
superior half of the movie in my opinion
and this is because it's not until this
在我看来,这部电影的上上半半部 在我看来,这是 因为它不是直到这个
这是因为直到这个
and this is because it's not until this
point when Buzz and Woody finally
这是因为直到这个时候 巴斯和伍迪终于
当巴斯和胡迪终于
point when Buzz and Woody finally
realized their flaws and the only way to
巴斯和伍迪终于意识到他们的缺陷 并且是唯一的方法
的缺陷,以及实现
realized their flaws and the only way to
overcome them due to the fact that they
克服这些缺陷的唯一办法,因为:
因为他们已克服了这些障碍,
overcome them due to the fact that they
are now in the worst situation they've
因为他们现在的处境最糟糕
他们现在的处境最糟糕
are now in the worst situation they've
ever been in they basically have to rely
他们现在的处境最糟糕 他们基本上不得不依赖
基本上必须依靠他们
ever been in they basically have to rely
on each other to get out of situations
基本上他们必须互相依靠 才能摆脱困境
为了摆脱困境
on each other to get out of situations
but even still they continue you to be
为了摆脱困境 彼此彼此彼此彼此 但仍会继续你
即便他们仍然会继续你
but even still they continue you to be
stubborn at least until Buzz finally
但即使他们仍然坚持你 固执,至少直到巴斯最后
至少直到巴斯最终
stubborn at least until Buzz finally
realizes the truth about what he really
至少直到巴兹终于意识到 他真实的真相
了解他真实的真相
realizes the truth about what he really
is and completely loses all sense of
完全失去所有感知
reality in the process because the
并且完全失去所有现实感,因为
之所以在这一进程中出现现实,是因为:
reality in the process because the
problem is he now realizes that the
因为问题是他现在意识到
问题是他现在意识到
problem is he now realizes that the
person he's been constantly arguing with
问题是他现在意识到 他一直和他争论的人
他一直在不断争吵
person he's been constantly arguing with
this entire time has been right and then
这个人一直在不断争吵 这整个时间 一直是正确的,然后
这整个时间 一直是正确的,然后
this entire time has been right and then
everything he thought he believed was
整个整个时间都是对的 然后他以为他相信的一切都是对的
他所相信的一切都是
everything he thought he believed was
wrong and now he has no sense of purpose
他以为他相信的一切都是错的 而现在他没有目的感
而现在他没有目的感,
wrong and now he has no sense of purpose
whatsoever and unfortunately for him
现在他毫无目的,不幸地为他而战
不论他为他而遭何报答和不幸,
whatsoever and unfortunately for him
Woody's main priority is still just
但不幸的是,胡迪的重中之重 仍然只是
伍迪的主要优先事项仍然是
Woody's main priority is still just
getting back to Andy's house and it's
伍迪的主要优先事项仍然是 回到安迪的房子,这是
回到安迪的房子,这是
getting back to Andy's house and it's
not until he fails to convince the
回到Andy的家里 直到他无法说服
直到他无法说服
not until he fails to convince the
others that buzz is his friend now that
直到他无法说服其他人 嗡嗡声是他现在的朋友
其他人的嗡嗡声是他现在的朋友
others that buzz is his friend now that
he finally realizes that there's nothing
现在他终于意识到 什么都没有了
他终于意识到 什么都没有
he finally realizes that there's nothing
he can do oh and also this ties back to
他终于意识到 他无能为力
他可以做哦, 和这个联系 回到
he can do oh and also this ties back to
the part where the toys tried to throw
他可以做哦,还有这个联系 回到玩具想扔的那部分
玩具想扔的那部分
the part where the toys tried to throw
him out the window proving that they
玩具试图把他扔出窗外 证明他们
他走出窗外 证明他们
him out the window proving that they
weren't truly his friends after all and
他走出窗外 证明他们不是真正的朋友
毕竟不是他真正的朋友
weren't truly his friends after all and
it is here when Woody finally realizes
伍迪终于意识到
当伍迪终于意识到
it is here when Woody finally realizes
that they aren't truly his friends as he
当伍迪终于意识到 他们不是他真正的朋友
他们不是他真正的朋友
that they aren't truly his friends as he
thought they were because his concept of
他们不是他真正的朋友 他以为他们是朋友 因为他的概念
因为他认为
thought they were because his concept of
what made someone his friend was based
因为他对什么能让他的朋友 成为他朋友的基地的概念
是什么让他的朋友成为他的基地
what made someone his friend was based
on the idea of whether they liked him or
是什么让某人成为他的朋友 是基于他们喜欢他还是喜欢他
他们究竟是喜悦他呢?还是喜悦他呢?
on the idea of whether they liked him or
not not a mutually beneficial
他们究竟喜不喜欢他,还是不喜欢他呢?
并非互利互惠互利
not not a mutually beneficial
relationship between both parties and
双方不能建立互利关系,双方不能建立互利关系。
双方间关系的关系以及
relationship between both parties and
unfortunately for him his misconceptions
双方关系的关系,而不幸的是,他对他的误解
不幸地为他而悲哀地说,他的错误的误解,
unfortunately for him his misconceptions
have left him lonelier than ever in his
不幸地,他的误解使他比以往任何时候都更加孤独。
使他更加孤单,
have left him lonelier than ever in his
mind he was so certain that just
使他比以前更加孤独 在他的脑海里,他是如此的确定,
他非常确信
mind he was so certain that just
bringing buzz back or some sort of proof
他非常肯定,他只是 带回嗡嗡回来或某种证据
带回铃声或某种证据
bringing buzz back or some sort of proof
that buzz really wasn't pushed out the
来回回回回回的嗡嗡声 或者某种证据 即嗡嗡声真的没有被推出
那种嗡嗡声真的没有被推出
that buzz really wasn't pushed out the
window by him would get back everything
他真的没把铃声从窗外推出来 就能把一切都拿回来
被他窗边的窗边 就能把一切都拿回来
window by him would get back everything
he thought he had but there's a lie he's
他用窗边的窗边 就能拿回一切 他以为他拥有的一切 但是他撒谎了
他以为他有 但有一个谎言,他
he thought he had but there's a lie he's
been telling himself finally proves to
他以为他有 但有一个谎言 他一直在自言自语 最终证明
最终证明
been telling himself finally proves to
hold a no wait whatsoever when it is put
他自己告诉自己 最终证明 毫不等待 当它被放
绝不等待着,当它被投入火刑的时候,
hold a no wait whatsoever when it is put
to the test and so now in their darkest
当它被考验的时候,你们绝不要等待什么等待,直到他们陷于最黑暗的状态。
现在他们最黑暗的黑暗中
to the test and so now in their darkest
moment when both characters believe that
现在在他们最黑暗的时刻 当两个角色都相信
当两个字符都相信
moment when both characters believe that
there's nothing left for either of them
当两个角色都相信 自己一无所有的时候
他们俩都一无所有了
there's nothing left for either of them
they finally realize the value in what
他们俩都一无所有 他们终于意识到什么是价值
他们最终认识到什么是价值
they finally realize the value in what
each other had that they didn't and as
他们终于意识到彼此拥有的价值 彼此没有的价值
彼此彼此彼此没有
each other had that they didn't and as
Woody finally reveals the truth in that
因为伍迪终于揭示了真相
伍迪终于揭示了真相
Woody finally reveals the truth in that
he thought he could never be as good as
伍迪终于揭露了真相 因为他认为他永远无法像
他以为他永远无法像
he thought he could never be as good as
Buzz this causes Buzz to realize that
他认为他永远不可能像巴兹那样好 这让巴兹意识到
巴斯这让巴斯意识到
Buzz this causes Buzz to realize that
all of Woody's actions were not because
巴斯,这让巴斯 巴斯意识到胡迪的所有行动 并不是因为
胡迪的所作所为不是因为
all of Woody's actions were not because
he disliked him but because he was
胡迪的所作所为 不是因为他不喜欢他 而是因为他
他不喜欢他,但因为他是
he disliked him but because he was
afraid of losing something and that this
他不喜欢他 但是因为他害怕失去一些东西
害怕失去一些东西和这个
afraid of losing something and that this
idea that he had no value whatsoever if
害怕失去一些东西 害怕失去一些东西
认为他没有任何价值
idea that he had no value whatsoever if
he wasn't really A Space Ranger couldn't
认为他没有价值 如果他不是真正的太空游骑兵
他不是真正的太空游骑兵
he wasn't really A Space Ranger couldn't
possibly be true if Woody saw so much
他不是真的太空游骑兵 如果伍迪看到这么多 就不可能是真的
万一伍迪看到这么多
possibly be true if Woody saw so much
value in him that he was afraid that he
如果伍迪认为他有如此多的价值 以至于他害怕他
以至於敬畏者,
value in him that he was afraid that he
would replace him and it finally becomes
因为他怕他取代他,而他最终变成
将取代他,最终成为
would replace him and it finally becomes
clear to him that being a toy is
最终他明白当玩具
向他证明,做一个玩具,确是一个玩具,
clear to him that being a toy is
actually a good thing and if it weren't
告诉他当玩具其实是件好事 如果不是
其实是件好事,如果不是
actually a good thing and if it weren't
for the hardships he went through with
其实是件好事 如果不是因为他经历的艰难
因他所遭的困苦,
for the hardships he went through with
Woody he never would have realized that
和伍迪一起经历的艰难 他永远不会意识到
伍迪他永远不会意识到
Woody he never would have realized that
and Woody now finally having given up
胡迪他永远不会意识到 胡迪现在终于放弃了
伍迪终于放弃了
and Woody now finally having given up
trying to prove that he's better than
伍迪终于放弃了 试图证明他比
试图证明他比
trying to prove that he's better than
Buzz because he realizes that it is all
试图证明他比巴斯好 因为他意识到
巴斯 因为他意识到这一切
Buzz because he realizes that it is all
pointless in the end finally he starts
巴斯,因为他意识到 这一切都毫无意义 最终,他终于开始
最终他终于开始毫无意义了
pointless in the end finally he starts
to see the value in Buzz the primary
最终毫无意义 他终于开始看到 在巴斯的主要价值
以查看在 Buzz 中的值为主
to see the value in Buzz the primary
thing that was stopping them from being
看到巴斯的价值 最主要的是阻止他们成为
阻止他们成为
thing that was stopping them from being
friends before we are the next
阻止他们在我们成为下一个朋友之前成为朋友
在我们成为下一个朋友之前
friends before we are the next
Companions of all of us and one of my
在我们成为我们的下一个伙伴之前,我们是朋友们的朋友,我也是其中之一,
我们所有人的同伴 和我的一位朋友
Companions of all of us and one of my
favorite things about how Buzz and Woody
我们所有人的同伴 以及我最喜欢的 巴斯和伍迪的故事之一
巴斯和胡迪的最爱
favorite things about how Buzz and Woody
finally become friends at this moment is
关于巴兹和胡迪 终于成为朋友的最爱
此时此刻终于成为朋友
finally become friends at this moment is
that it all ties back to how Andy
此时此刻终于成为朋友 这一切都和Andy的关系有关
都和Andy有关
that it all ties back to how Andy
treated both of them and even though
和Andy对待他们俩的方式有关 即使
他们俩受优待,彼此间也受优待,即使
treated both of them and even though
Woody is Andy's favorite toy he values
虽然伍迪是安迪最喜欢的玩具
伍迪是安迪最喜欢的玩具 他珍视的玩具
Woody is Andy's favorite toy he values
all the toys still the same when Woody
伍迪是安迪最喜欢的玩具 他珍惜所有的玩具
伍迪的时候所有的玩具都一样
all the toys still the same when Woody
was the only toy there andy loved him
当胡迪是唯一的玩具时 所有的玩具都是一样的
只有玩具 在那里,安迪爱他
was the only toy there andy loved him
unconditionally and Woody
是唯一的玩具 在那里,安迪爱他无条件 和伍迪
和无条件的胡迪
unconditionally and Woody
unconditionally loved him back and
和胡迪无条件 无条件爱他回来,
无条件爱他
unconditionally loved him back and
Andy's unconditional love for Woody is
Andy对伍迪的无条件爱是
安迪无条件的爱胡迪就是
Andy's unconditional love for Woody is
proven in Toy Story 2 when he chooses to
安迪对胡迪无条件的爱 在玩具故事2中证明 当他选择
在玩具故事2中,当他选择
proven in Toy Story 2 when he chooses to
still love him and play with him even
在玩具故事2中,当他选择 仍然爱他 和他玩
仍然爱他,而且与他一起游戏;
still love him and play with him even
though his arm got ripped and Andy was
即使他的手臂被撕裂 Andy 也依然爱着他 和他一起玩耍
虽然他的手臂被撕裂 Andy是
though his arm got ripped and Andy was
the only person in the entire house who
虽然他的手臂被撕裂 Andy是整个房子里唯一
整个房屋中唯一
the only person in the entire house who
Woody saw as Superior to him and when he
整个房子里唯一一个人 胡迪认为他是他的至高无上 当他
伍迪视胡迪为他至高无上 当他
Woody saw as Superior to him and when he
became lost both Andy and Woody were
伍迪视他为贵族 当他迷失的时候 Andy和伍迪都
安迪和胡迪都失踪了
became lost both Andy and Woody were
worried about each other's safety
安迪和胡迪都失去双亲 担心对方的安全
担心对方的安全
worried about each other's safety
because they both cared about each other
担心对方的安全 因为他们都关心对方
因为他们都互相关心
because they both cared about each other
in this relationship unlike how Woody
因为他们都关心彼此 在这种关系中 不像伍迪
和伍迪不同
in this relationship unlike how Woody
treated Buzz where he immediately tried
和伍迪对待巴斯的方式不同 他在那里立即进行了审判
治疗巴兹,他在那里被立即审判
treated Buzz where he immediately tried
to put him down instead of offering his
他立即试图把他放下来,而不是提供他的
使他放下来,而舍他而敬事他,
to put him down instead of offering his
hand out in friendship he chose to love
将他放下来,而不是为他所选择爱的友谊而献出手来。
与他所爱的友情相交,
hand out in friendship he chose to love
him conditionally only if he submitted
以友谊相交,他只选择有条件地爱他,只当他归顺。
只有在他提交
him conditionally only if he submitted
to him and did not take away his power
只有服从他,而且不丧失他的权力,他才有条件地接受他;
他没有丧失他的权力,也没有丧失他的权力,
to him and did not take away his power
or influence I and as we can see when
他没有夺走他的权力或影响力,我和我们所见的,
或影响我和我们所看到的
or influence I and as we can see when
Woody and Buzz do eventually get back to
或影响我和我们可以看到 当胡迪和巴兹最终回到
胡迪和巴兹最终会回到
Woody and Buzz do eventually get back to
Andy he is equally thrilled to have
胡迪和巴兹最终会回到安迪身边 他同样兴奋
安迪,他同样高兴有
Andy he is equally thrilled to have
found both of them because he doesn't
安迪,他同样兴奋地找到了他们两个 因为他没有
发现他们两个 因为他没有
found both of them because he doesn't
actually value Woody or Buzz more than
因为他并不真正重视胡迪或巴斯
实际值为 Wood 或 Buzz 或 Buzz 大于
actually value Woody or Buzz more than
the other as Woody had feared but he
事实上,胡迪或巴斯比其他人更看重胡迪或巴斯,正如胡迪所担心的,但他
和伍迪所畏惧的一样,
the other as Woody had feared but he
cares about them equally and it should
和伍迪所畏惧的一样 但他同样关心他们 并且应该关心他们
你们应当公平地慈爱他们,他们应当平等享受;
cares about them equally and it should
also be noted as well that even though
他们同样关心他们,也值得指出的是,尽管
也值得注意到,尽管
also be noted as well that even though
he doesn't show it as much in the first
也值得注意的是,即使他没有在第一个
第一次他没有表现出那么多
he doesn't show it as much in the first
two movies Andy also clearly really
安迪在前两部电影里 并没有展示得那么多 安迪也非常清楚
两部电影 Andy也非常清楚
two movies Andy also clearly really
cares about the other toys as well since
两部电影 Andy显然也非常关心其他玩具
从此以后,其他玩具也关心其他玩具
cares about the other toys as well since
he is so unwilling to get rid of them in
也关心其他玩具 因为他如此不愿意在
他如此不愿意摆脱他们
he is so unwilling to get rid of them in
Toy Story 3. well except for a couple of
他如此不愿意在玩具第3号故事中摆脱他们 除了一对夫妇
玩具第3号,除了几个
Toy Story 3. well except for a couple of
forgettable Side characters but uh
玩具第3号故事 除了几个可以忘却的侧边人物
侧边字符,但uh
forgettable Side characters but uh
that's not the point it all comes back
可忘却的侧边字符,但 呃,这不是重点 这一切会回来
这不是重点 这一切都会回来
that's not the point it all comes back
to the fact that he's never known a
这不是重点 它的一切 回到事实 他从来没有听说过一个
他从不知道
to the fact that he's never known a
world where someone was treated the same
事实上,他从未认识过 世界上有人 受到同样的待遇
在一个世界里,有人受到同样的待遇
world where someone was treated the same
as him he was always above everyone else
在一个世界上,有人得到与他一样的待遇 他总是凌驾于所有人之上
因为他总是凌驾于所有人之上
as him he was always above everyone else
and as soon as someone else comes to
因为他总是凌驾于所有人之上 并且一旦有人来
等别人一来
and as soon as someone else comes to
challenge that position it causes him to
一旦别人来挑战这个立场 就会引起他
挑战这一地位,导致他
challenge that position it causes him to
act illogically it is Woody's irrational
这是伍迪的不理性行为
胡迪的行为不合逻辑 这是胡迪的无理行为
act illogically it is Woody's irrational
fear of losing something that he already
这是伍迪失去他已经失去的东西的 毫无理性的恐惧
害怕失去他已经失去的东西
fear of losing something that he already
has that got them into this situation in
害怕失去他已经失去的东西 让他们陷入这种境地
导致他们陷入这种情况
has that got them into this situation in
the first place but it is a rational
但却是理性的,
虽说这是常道,却是理性的,
the first place but it is a rational
fear of true danger that finally causes
但它是对真实危险的理性恐惧,最终导致
担心最终造成真正危险的真正危险
fear of true danger that finally causes
him and Buzz to come together in the end
最终导致他和巴兹 最终走到一起
他和巴兹最终会走到一起
him and Buzz to come together in the end
Woody was so focused on what he had to
他和巴兹一起来到 最终胡迪 如此专注于他必须做什么
伍迪如此专注于
Woody was so focused on what he had to
lose that he never considered what he
伍迪如此专注于失去他所失去的东西 以至于他从未考虑过他所失去的东西
未曾记念过自己所丧失的(偶像),
lose that he never considered what he
had to gain instead however in the end
因为他从未考虑过自己要获得什么,然而,最后却失去了什么,
但最终却得取而代之
had to gain instead however in the end
all these things combined together along
然而,最终,所有这些事情加在一起,总合起来,反而得到了好处。
将所有这些事物结合在一起,
all these things combined together along
with the fact that they had to go
所有这些事情加在一起, 以及他们必须去的事实
和他们必须去的事实
with the fact that they had to go
through so many trial and tribulations
他们不得不经历如此多的磨难和磨难
通过如此多的考验和磨难
through so many trial and tribulations
together many of which they would not
通过如此多的考验和磨难 和许多他们不会
他们常常在一起,而不能在一起;
together many of which they would not
have overcome if it weren't for each of
如果不是每个人的,他们不可能战胜其中的很多,如果不是其中的每一个
如果不是每一个都克服了
have overcome if it weren't for each of
them using their unique abilities in
如果不是每个人利用自己独特的能力
利用他们的独特能力
them using their unique abilities in
each situation that the other one
在每种情况下,他们利用各自独特的能力,而另一种情况是:
两种情况中,另一情况是:
each situation that the other one
couldn't do something I said in my
每一个情况 对方都无法做 我对我说过的话
我无法做我所说的话
couldn't do something I said in my
Monsters University video a while back
刚才在怪兽大学的视频里 我无法做我所说的话
大学的录像片 前一阵子
Monsters University video a while back
that equally applies to this movie if
大学前一段时间的录像 同样适用于这部电影
这同样适用于这部电影,如果
that equally applies to this movie if
not even more so is that the strongest
这一点同样适用于这部电影,如果不是比这部电影更强,那么最强的
最强者,更强者,更强者,
not even more so is that the strongest
bonds are those that are forged in fire
最强烈的纽带就是那些在烈火中伪造的纽带。
这等人,是用火制伪造的,
bonds are those that are forged in fire
it's because they had to go through so
是那些在火中伪造的债券 是因为他们不得不经历
因为他们不得不经历这样的经历
it's because they had to go through so
many hardships together that they know
因为他们不得不一起经历如此多的困苦 他们知道
他们所知道的多难,多难,
many hardships together that they know
they can trust each other in the end oh
一起经历许多困难 他们知道他们可以信任对方 最终哦
最终他们可以互相信任哦
they can trust each other in the end oh
and did I mention the main theme of this
最终他们可以互相信任 哦,我有没有提到这个主题
并且我是否提到这个主题的主题
and did I mention the main theme of this
movie
我是否提到这部电影的主题
yes that one which is not just a perfect
(a) 不单单是完美无缺的,
main theme for this movie because of the
不只是这部电影的完美主题,因为
这部电影的主题主题
main theme for this movie because of the
fact that it's a song about friendship
这部电影的主题 因为它是一首关于友谊的歌曲
事实上,这是一首歌 关于友谊
fact that it's a song about friendship
and the whole theme of the movie is
事实上,这是一首歌 关于友谊 和整部电影的主题
整个电影的主题是
and the whole theme of the movie is
about being a true friend and what that
整个电影的主题是 做一个真正的朋友,什么
做一个真正的朋友和什么
about being a true friend and what that
actually means one of the most clever
当一个真正的朋友 这实际上意味着什么 最聪明的人之一
其实是最聪明的人之一
actually means one of the most clever
things about this song is how it plays
意思是这首歌最聪明的一点 就是它是如何演奏的
有关这首歌的事情 就是它是如何演奏的
things about this song is how it plays
at the beginning with Woody and Andy and
有关这首歌的事情 是它如何在开始 与伍迪和安迪
从伍迪和安迪开始
at the beginning with Woody and Andy and
so you think it must be referring to
从伍迪和安迪开始 所以你认为这必须是指
因此,你认为它必须是指
so you think it must be referring to
them but the lyrics more so match the
所以,你认为它必须 指的是他们,但歌词 更符合
但歌词更符合
them but the lyrics more so match the
journey that Buzz and Woody go through
但歌词更符合巴斯和胡迪的旅程
巴斯和胡迪经历的旅程
journey that Buzz and Woody go through
on this adventure and both of these
巴斯和胡迪经历这次冒险 和这两个
这两场冒险的探险
on this adventure and both of these
points are actually very deliberate
这两点其实都是深思熟虑的
要点实际上是非常慎重的
points are actually very deliberate
because it shows us that Woody needs to
这一点其实是非常深思熟虑的 因为它向我们表明伍迪需要
因为它向我们表明伍迪需要
because it shows us that Woody needs to
make a friendship the strength of the
因为它向我们表明 伍迪需要把友谊
使友谊成为世界的力量
make a friendship the strength of the
one that he has with Andy with Buzz or
友谊就是他和安迪和巴兹的友谊的力量
和他和安迪和巴兹在一起
one that he has with Andy with Buzz or
he'll never make it through to the end
和安弟和巴斯在一起 否则他撑不下去
他到最后都撑不过去
he'll never make it through to the end
but on top of that the way it is worded
他永远到不了最后 但除此之外,它用词的方式
但除此以外,一切言辞都是这样的:
but on top of that the way it is worded
is also really clever in my opinion
但除此之外, 这个词的用词方式 在我看来也是非常聪明的
在我看来,我也很聪明
is also really clever in my opinion
because it's not you are my friend it's
在我看来 也非常聪明 因为这不是你 我的朋友,这是
因为你不是我的朋友
because it's not you are my friend it's
You've Got a Friend in Me and the key
因为你不是我的朋友 是因为你有我朋友和钥匙
你有我朋友和钥匙
You've Got a Friend in Me and the key
difference here being that you have to
你有我的一个朋友 关键区别在于你必须
区别在于你必须
difference here being that you have to
be a friend to someone else before
区别在于 你之前必须成为别人的朋友
以前是别人的朋友
be a friend to someone else before
they'll be a friend back to you it's a
成为别人的朋友 在他们成为朋友 回到你身边之前
他们会成为朋友回到你身边
they'll be a friend back to you it's a
matter of trust it has to go both ways
他们会成为朋友 回到你身边 这是信任的问题 它必须双向合作
信任的事物 它必须双向走
matter of trust it has to go both ways
or it doesn't work someone can say that
信任的事情 它必须双向走 或它不工作 有人可以说,
或它不工作 或它不工作 有人可以说,
or it doesn't work someone can say that
they're your friend but it doesn't
或者说不管用,有人可以说 他们是你的朋友,但事实并非如此
他们是你的朋友 但不是朋友
they're your friend but it doesn't
actually mean anything if they don't
他们是你的朋友 但如果他们不这么做 也不代表什么
如果他们不这样做,实际上意味着什么
actually mean anything if they don't
actually stick up to that one-sided
其实意味着什么 如果他们不真正 坚持到那个单向的
实际上坚持到那个片面的
actually stick up to that one-sided
relationships where you only rely on
实际上坚持着这种片面的关系, 你只能依靠这种关系
关系中您仅依赖的关系
relationships where you only rely on
other people to do things for you it's
关系的关系,你只依靠 其他人为你做事情 这是
其他人为你做事情
other people to do things for you it's
not what makes a true friend at all and
别人为你做事情 根本不是真正的朋友
却不能做一个真正的朋友,
not what makes a true friend at all and
that's why having this song say you are
是什么使一个真正的朋友 根本不是什么, 这就是为什么有这首歌 说,你是
这就是为什么有这首歌 说你是
that's why having this song say you are
my friend would feel so much more empty
这就是为什么有这首歌 说你是我的朋友 会觉得更空虚
我的朋友会觉得自己空空无一物
my friend would feel so much more empty
than You've Got a Friend in Me because
我朋友会觉得空虚 比你有我朋友的空虚多了
你有一个朋友在我的朋友,因为
than You've Got a Friend in Me because
it would be the equivalent of calling
比起你在我这里有个朋友 因为这相当于打来电话
相当于打来电话
it would be the equivalent of calling
someone else a friend without them
等于说别人是朋友,没有他们
一个朋友,没有他们
someone else a friend without them
returning the favor back and of course
一个朋友,没有他们回来的恩惠 当然
回来还你恩情,当然了
returning the favor back and of course
that's not the only clever lyric there's
当然,这不是唯一聪明的歌词
这不是唯一聪明的歌词
that's not the only clever lyric there's
other stuff like how it says you've got
这不是唯一聪明的歌词 还有其他的东西 比如它说你有
其他的东西,比如它如何 说,你有
other stuff like how it says you've got
troubles and I've got them too but if we
其它的东西,比如 上面说你有麻烦 我也有麻烦,但如果我们
麻烦和我也有,但如果
troubles and I've got them too but if we
stick together we can see it through and
麻烦和我也有,但如果我们团结在一起 就能看穿它
紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧
stick together we can see it through and
that there isn't anything I wouldn't do
团结在一起,我们就能看穿它 并且没有任何我不愿做的事
我什么也不会做
that there isn't anything I wouldn't do
for you it's a completely selfless song
这首歌是一首无私无私的歌
对于你来说,这是一首完全无私的歌
for you it's a completely selfless song
which perfectly encapsulates everything
这是一首完全无私无私的歌 完美地包封了一切
完全封装一切事物
which perfectly encapsulates everything
it means to be a true friend and all
完美包罗一切 意味着做一个真正的朋友和所有的一切
意思是成为真正的朋友
it means to be a true friend and all
this pays off in the end when Woody
意思是成为真正的朋友 而这一切最终都会得到回报 当伍迪
当伍迪最终得到回报时
this pays off in the end when Woody
realizes that now that the other toys
当伍迪意识到,现在其他玩具
已经意识到,现在, 其它玩具
realizes that now that the other toys
don't believe him the only person who he
已经意识到,现在其他玩具 不相信他 唯一一个人,他
不要相信他 唯一相信他的人
don't believe him the only person who he
truly trusts and who can trust him back
不要相信他 他唯一信任的人 唯一可以信任他的人
真心信任他,谁能信任他
truly trusts and who can trust him back
is Buzz and he refuses to leave without
真正的信任和谁能信任他,谁可以信任他 巴斯是巴兹,他拒绝离开,没有
巴斯和他拒绝离开
is Buzz and he refuses to leave without
saving him which of course leads to this
巴斯就是巴斯,他拒绝离境,但他不救他,他不肯出境。
拯救他,而他使他成功。
saving him which of course leads to this
absolutely outstanding scene
保存他,这当然 导致这个绝对 突出的场景
anything
任何
I get goosebumps every time and also
任何我得到 鹅蛋 每次,而且
每次我得到鹅蛋 每一次,而且
I get goosebumps every time and also
something I really like about this part
每次我得到鹅蛋 和一些我很喜欢的关于这部分的东西
我对这部分真的很喜欢
something I really like about this part
where after defeating Sid Buzz gets
我很喜欢这个部分 击败Sid Buzz之后
击败Sid Buzz之后
where after defeating Sid Buzz gets
stuck on the fence but Woody has the
击败Sid Buzz之后 被困在栅栏上
被困在栅栏上,但伍迪有
stuck on the fence but Woody has the
opportunity to escape back to Andy's
但伍迪有机会逃回安迪家
逃回Andy家的机会
opportunity to escape back to Andy's
house he doesn't go back to save Buzz
逃回Andy家的机会 他不会回去救Buzz
房子他不回去救巴斯
house he doesn't go back to save Buzz
out of obligation he does so because he
他不会回去救巴斯 逃避义务,他这样做,因为他
他这样做是出于义务,因为他
out of obligation he does so because he
genuinely cares and doesn't want to
他这样做是出于义务,因为他真正关心和不想
真正关心和不想
genuinely cares and doesn't want to
leave Buzz behind showing just how much
真正关心自己 不想丢下巴斯 证明自己有多在乎
巴斯留下的巴斯 展示了多少
leave Buzz behind showing just how much
he's changed since they first met it's
巴斯离开巴斯 显示他多少 变化了自从他们第一次见面
自从他们第一次见面后 他变了
he's changed since they first met it's
only now when Woody is putting all his
自从他们第一次见面后 他已经变了 现在才是伍迪
只有在伍迪把
only now when Woody is putting all his
energy and effort into saving Buzz
直到伍迪把精力和精力 都投入到救巴兹的手中
将精力和精力 投入到拯救巴斯
energy and effort into saving Buzz
Lightyear that the other toys finally
为了拯救巴斯光年 其他玩具最终
光之年 其他玩具终于
Lightyear that the other toys finally
realize that he actually does care and
光年 其他玩具终于意识到 他确实关心和关心
他意识到他实际上关心和关心
realize that he actually does care and
that if he could come to a point where
他意识到,他实际上确实关心,如果他能够达到以下一点:
假若他达到一个目的,
that if he could come to a point where
he considers Buzz a true friend and
如果他能说到一个道理,他认为巴斯是一个真正的朋友,
他认为巴斯是一个真正的朋友
he considers Buzz a true friend and
would do anything to save him and not
他认为巴斯是一个真正的朋友 愿意做任何事来救他 而不是
为了救他,不为他做任何事
would do anything to save him and not
leave him behind then they can once
为了救他,不抛下他,他们能做任何事。
离开他,他们就可以一次地离开他。
leave him behind then they can once
again finally trust him and by the time
然后他们就能再次信任他 最终相信他
最终再次信任他 并相信他
again finally trust him and by the time
the next movie starts he'll have
等到下一部电影开始的时候 他就会拥有
下一部电影开始 他将拥有
the next movie starts he'll have
actually made True bonds and
下部电影开始 他实际上会 已经做了真实债券,
真实债券和
actually made True bonds and
relationships with all the other toys
和所有其它玩具的 真实债券和关系
与所有其他玩具的关系
relationships with all the other toys
showing just how important this entire
与所有其他玩具的关系 显示了这整个过程有多重要
仅仅显示这整个过程有多重要
showing just how important this entire
Adventure was for him as a person and
展示整个冒险对他作为一个人有多重要
冒险是为了他一个人
Adventure was for him as a person and
not just his relationship with buzz but
冒险是为了他作为一个人 不只是他和嗡嗡声的关系
不只是他和嗡嗡声的关系
not just his relationship with buzz but
his relationship with everyone and
不只是他和嗡嗡声的关系 还有他和每个人的关系
他与每个人的关系,以及
his relationship with everyone and
lastly as the cherry on top of the whole
他与每个人的关系 最后作为樱桃 凌驾于整个世界之上
以樱桃为顶端
lastly as the cherry on top of the whole
story the only way that Woody is able to
最后作为整个故事的顶端的樱桃 胡迪唯一能够做到的方法
胡迪唯一能够
story the only way that Woody is able to
gain back the reputation and power that
只有这样胡迪才能 恢复名誉和权力
获得声誉和权力
gain back the reputation and power that
he lost is to do the one thing he should
赢得他失去的名誉和权力 就是做他应该做的一件事
他输了就是做一件他应该做的事
he lost is to do the one thing he should
have done in the first place befriend
他输了就是做一件他本该做的事 一开始就交朋友
交了朋友 交了朋友 交了朋友 交了朋友 交了朋友
have done in the first place befriend
Buzz Lightyear and treat him as an equal
第一次成为朋友巴斯光年 并同等对待他
巴斯光年 以平等的态度对待他
Buzz Lightyear and treat him as an equal
to everyone else oh and also a Nazi
巴斯光年,视他为 与其他人平等,哦,还有纳粹
以及纳粹的纳粹
to everyone else oh and also a Nazi
himself as superior to the other toys
和纳粹自己比其他玩具更优越
自己比其他玩具更优越
himself as superior to the other toys
either and well that is why I believe
自己也比其他玩具更优越 所以我相信
和好,这就是为什么我相信
either and well that is why I believe
Toy Story is one of the greatest Tales
这也是为什么我相信玩具故事 是最伟大的故事之一
玩具故事是最伟大的故事之一
Toy Story is one of the greatest Tales
of Friendship ever told and is still one
玩具故事是有史以来最伟大的友谊故事之一 至今仍是
友情永不忘怀
of Friendship ever told and is still one
of the greatest animated movies ever
友谊是有史以来最伟大的动画片之一
有史以来最伟大的动画电影
of the greatest animated movies ever
made in my opinion I mean imagine if
最动动动的电影
在我的见解中 我意思是想象一下
made in my opinion I mean imagine if
this movie was bad traditional animation
想象这部电影是不是 不好的传统动画片
这部电影是不好的传统动画
this movie was bad traditional animation
would probably still be alive wait
这部电影是不好的 传统动画动画 可能还会活着等待
可能还会活着等待
would probably still be alive wait
that's a good thing well now I would
可能还会活着 等待是件好事 现在好,我会的
这是件好事,现在我愿意
that's a good thing well now I would
like to know what all of you think about
这是件好事,现在我想知道 你们都在想什么
想知道你们都在想什么
like to know what all of you think about
Toy Story in the comments down below and
想知道大家在下面的评论中 是怎么看待玩具故事的
下面的评论和下面的评论中的玩具故事
Toy Story in the comments down below and
if you think there is some sort of
玩具故事在下面的评论中 下下来的评论 如果你认为有某种
如果你认为有某种
if you think there is some sort of
better Story of Friendship in another
如果你认为有某种 更好的友谊故事 在另一个
更好的友谊故事
better Story of Friendship in another
movie or show that I haven't talked
更好的友谊故事 在另一部电影 或节目,我没有说话
电影或表演,我没有说话
movie or show that I haven't talked
about or can't remember off the top of
电影或节目,我没有谈论 或不记得
或无法记起
about or can't remember off the top of
my head if you enjoyed the video then
或不记得我头顶上 或不记得了 如果你喜欢这段视频,然后
如果你喜欢那段视频的话
my head if you enjoyed the video then
you can do more than just like And
如果你喜欢这段视频... ...那你就可以做更多的事... ...不只是像...
你可以做更多 不只是像和
you can do more than just like And
subscribe and you could also follow me
你可以做更多的事 不只是喜欢,可以订阅,也可以跟着我
你也可以跟我去订户,也可以跟着我
subscribe and you could also follow me
on several social media platforms that I
并且你也可以追随我, 在几个社交媒体平台上,
在几个社交媒体平台上,
on several social media platforms that I
appear on links in the description down
在几个社交媒体平台上, 我出现在下面描述的链接上。
显示在下方描述的链接中
appear on links in the description down
below I'd also like to remind you to
下面描述的链接中显示的链接中,我还要提醒你
下面我还想提醒你
below I'd also like to remind you to
check out my gaming channel where I post
我还想提醒你 看我的赌博频道
检查我的赌博频道 在那里我张贴
check out my gaming channel where I post
gaming videos occasionally not super
查查我的赌博频道 在那里我张贴赌博视频 偶尔不是超级
游戏视频偶而不是超级
gaming videos occasionally not super
often but I do whenever I can find the
玩游戏视频偶而并不经常超常,但只要我能找到
但我经常做,每当我能找到
often but I do whenever I can find the
time to edit them Link in the
但每当我找到时间编辑它们时,我经常这样做。
编辑时间
time to edit them Link in the
description down below and if you want
编辑时间 编辑时间 链接 在下面和如果您想要的话的描述中
下面下面的描述,如果需要的话
description down below and if you want
to support me in a way further than just
下面的描述,如果你想 支持我的方式更进一步
更进一步支持我
to support me in a way further than just
my own videos then I have a patreon
支持我的方式 超越我自己的视频
我有自己的录影带,然后我有一个露天舞厅
my own videos then I have a patreon
which you can subscribe to where you can
我自己的视频 然后我有一个天台 你可以在可以订阅的地方订阅
在哪里可以订阅
which you can subscribe to where you can
see early videos and also get your name
您可以订阅早期视频,并获得您的姓名。
查看早期视频,并获得您的姓名
see early videos and also get your name
shouted out in the credits just like
看到早期的视频 并获得你的名字 大声喊出 在信用额中 就像
在信用额中大喊大叫 就像
shouted out in the credits just like
these people and Tyke Macabre mole in 7x
就像这些人和7x的泰克·麦卡布雷内奸一样
这些人和Tyke Macabre 7x的内鬼
these people and Tyke Macabre mole in 7x
Vos and Conor Harris or if you're not
这些人和Tyke Macabre内鬼 在7xVos和Conor Harris 或如果你不是
沃斯和康纳哈里斯 或者如果你不是
Vos and Conor Harris or if you're not
interested in patreon you could also
沃斯和康诺哈里斯 或者如果你对帕特雷恩不感兴趣 你也可以
您也可以对patreon感兴趣, 您也可以
interested in patreon you could also
support me by becoming a channel member
你也可以支持我成为频道成员
成为频道成员支持我
support me by becoming a channel member
doing so will give you a little badge
做一个频道成员来支持我 就能给你一个小徽章
这样做会给你一个小徽章
doing so will give you a little badge
next to your name as well as getting a
这样做会给你贴在名字旁边的小徽章 并给你一个
在您名字旁边的您的名字旁边, 并获得一个
next to your name as well as getting a
shout out at the end of my videos just
临Τи魁紇挡 羘
在我的视频结尾大喊大叫
shout out at the end of my videos just
like the patrons a big thank you to
在我的视频结尾大喊大叫 就像赞助者一样 非常感谢你
就像赞助者们感谢你们
like the patrons a big thank you to
Samir a Edward p Emperor Roku and
就像赞助者们感谢撒米尔 一位爱德华·波·罗库皇帝
萨米尔·爱德华·普·罗库皇帝和
Samir a Edward p Emperor Roku and
kalabunga but wait you there don't leave
沙米尔·爱德华·普·罗库和卡拉本加皇帝的罗库和卡拉邦加
卡拉邦加,但等待你在那里 不要离开
kalabunga but wait you there don't leave
this video just yet there's more great
卡拉邦加,但等待你在那里 不要离开这个视频 只是还有更多伟大的
这段视频还远不止于此
this video just yet there's more great
Rocco talk content for you to check out
这段视频还有些伟大的 Rocco 谈话内容要你查查
Rocco 说内容让你退房
Rocco talk content for you to check out
such as this video over here where I
Rocco谈内容 让你看看像这个视频这样的视频 在这里,我在这里
例如这段视频,在这里,我在那里
such as this video over here where I
talk about the villain Syndrome from The
比如这段视频,我在这里 谈论了来自The的恶棍综合症。
说到恶棍综合症
talk about the villain Syndrome from The
Incredibles or perhaps this video over
或这段录像
难以置信的 或可能是这段视频结束
Incredibles or perhaps this video over
here which is another Toy Story related
难以置信的或可能是这段视频 与玩具故事有关
这里还有另外一个玩具故事
here which is another Toy Story related
video that being my analysis of Toy
这是另一段玩具故事相关视频 是我对玩具的分析
视频是我对玩具的分析
video that being my analysis of Toy
Story 2. both are great videos if you
我对玩具故事2的分析 这两部影片都是很棒的
故事二,如果你
Story 2. both are great videos if you
have time to watch them but most
故事二,如果有时间看的话 这两部都是很棒的视频
有时间观察他们,但他们大半是监视的,
have time to watch them but most
importantly of all always remember to
有时间看着他们 但最重要的是永远记住
最重要的是永远记住
importantly of all always remember to
stay iconic
最重要的是 永远记得要保持标志性
保持图标
stay iconic
本字幕由AI大模型生成